Guide to the Ann Brewer Knox papers, 1935-2011 MS2305
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Poetry and short fiction, 1977-2011; Series 1
  - Drafts, 1977-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1
    - Knots, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Knots and other poems, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Laaben neulengbach, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Late march (towpath), 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Late snow, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Late spring, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Late summer story, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Learning to see a deer, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Letter, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Letter from moscow, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Lesson, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Lessons, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Light in bottles, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Little architechure / skull, circa 2005; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Little known bird of inner eye, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Little speech on death, 2005-2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Little victory, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Lolling about, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - London bridge, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Look down, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Looking across the fjord, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Lost pond, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Lovesong in a minor key, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Ludlum's dog, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Maggie, 2001-2003; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Maggie, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Maggie, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Maggie, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Magnus, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Magnus isn't here, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Man made, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Man on a roof looking down, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Map, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Mare, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Marmalade, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Marmalade, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Marsh, drumlin, hard-edges clouds, 2007-2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Marsh island, circa 1990; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Marsh island, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Mary jane, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Matter of balance, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Midsummer, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Milestone, circa 1996; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Mims, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Mims, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Mims, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Mims / 2 of us, 2000-2001; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Misc. drafts, circa 1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Misc. drafts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Misc. drafts, 2007-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Misc. drafts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Misc. drafts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Misc. drafts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Misc. drafts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Misc. poems, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Misc. poems, circa 1977; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Misc. poems, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Misc. poems, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Misc. publications and writings, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Moment to know everything, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Monday after thanksgiving, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Moonrise, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Morel, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Mother birthmark sufari portrait, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Moving on bonsai paulie sarah, 2000-2003; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Moving toward (the crone), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - My eye!, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - My favorite cousin's wife, circa 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - My friend listens to symphony, 2007-2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - My 65th wedding anniversary, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Names, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Names from the past, circa 2004; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Nefrititi's profile, 2005-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - New language, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - New word, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Newphew, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Next day (anniversary), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - No folder misc. poems, 2008-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - No freedom, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Nothing simple, 2008-2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Novel, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Novel - notes, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Old drafts, circa 1996-1999; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Old fellow with jaunty beret, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Old geologist, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Old men (woman's song), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Old poems, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Old poems (not on my laptop), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - On coming storm, circa 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - On not going to china, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - On receiving a bad review, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - One a day, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - One hundred years, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - One more journey, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Only once, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Origins, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Paco, circa 1986; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Paco, circa 1989; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Paco, circa 1990; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Palm, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Parachutist, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Path between houses, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Patronymic, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Paulie, circa 1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Paulie, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Paulie at the cultured pearl, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Paulie (bos), circa 2003; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Paulie leaves home, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Pelegeya, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Pharoah or monarch / migration, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Photograph of my mother, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Pier-glass, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Pieta, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Pilgrims (company of), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Poem drafts, circa 2003-2004; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Poem starts, fragments, notes, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Poem in form abk, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Poems old drafts, circa 2000-2001; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Poems to send, circa 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Poetry drafts, circa 2005-2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Poetry summer, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Possible poems drafts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Preparing to go, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Pretend, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Probing for light, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Procession of sound, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Promise, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Puppet dancer, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Questions, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Questions about love, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Ram's skull, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Ready, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Recent poems, 2010-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Recovering hostess, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Reflections for andrew, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Reflections in a mirror, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Return from the sea, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Rico, 1984-2001; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Rico, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Rico, 1999-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Righting oneself, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Ritual for a safe journey, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Ritual for divorce, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Rituals, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - River, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - River rising, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Rona chang, 2007-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Rona photos and poems, circa 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Rona poems, circa 2010-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Rona poems, circa 2009-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Room 204, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Rooms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Rooting out, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Rose, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Roses, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Roxy, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Roxy, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Roxy, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Rug market, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Rugs, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Safekeeping, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Safekeeping, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Salvation, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Sand, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Sand, circa 2001; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Sand / bones, circa 1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Sapling, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Sarah, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Sarah, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Sarah camp, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Sarah mountain, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Sarah mountain, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Sargasso sea, 2008-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Sayonara bonsai, circa 2002; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Sea ice, 2004-2005; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Sea-wall, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Secret, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Seems, 2007-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Self portrait, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Separation, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Separation, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Seven reasons I'm glad you're back, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Seventeen year locust, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Shadow, 2010-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - She cleans a trout, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - She names names, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - She remembers the first time, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Shedding, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Silk peddler, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Simple, circa 1987; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Simple, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Simple act, 2008-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Singing man, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Sixty first wedding anniversary, 2008-2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Skin, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Sloth, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Sloth, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Small sound large space, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Small things, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Small things, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Snails, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Snow day, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Snowscape with bird, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - So what's new?, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Something is happening, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Somewhere you've been before, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Sonnets starts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Son's leaving, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Son's visit, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Sorry, mouse, 2005-2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Sounds of cabarete, 1986; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Sounds of cabarete, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Stalled fast forward, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Start with rain, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Starts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Starts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Starts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Starts unfinished, 2006-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Staying in nowhere, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Stone, forest, song, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Stone tool, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Stonecrop, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Stop time, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Story starts, circa 2001-2002; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Street mime, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Summer of seventeen year locust, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Summer solstice, circa 1984; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Supercool, circa 1984; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Survivors, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Survivors, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Susan, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Syntax, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Taking shape, 2008-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Talk, 2009-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Tao, 2006-2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Tao, circa 2006; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Tao - added, 2006-2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Tao early drafts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Tao poems drafts, 2005-2006; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Tao poems drafts, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Thank you cavafy, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - That didn't hurt, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Thaw, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Thaw, 2008-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - There is no grace, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - These mountains, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Things as they are, 2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Things I haven't written about, 2010-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Things I haven't written about, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Things left undone, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Three men I loved, circa 1978; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Tiff, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Time of change / eagle in the rock, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Time out, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Time to go, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Time to go and other poems, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - To ask forgiveness, 2005-2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - To get past, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - To know a stone, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - To reckon distance / miles traveled, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - To see a deer, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - To take in music, 2007-2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Toad, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Trail of wandering angus, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Train to another country, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Train to another country, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Travellers, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Trek, circa 1994; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Trek, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Trio drafts, 2000-2003; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Trio - Eliz, Paulie, Sarah, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - True, circa 2009-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Turn, circa 2009-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Turned tables, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Two old women, 2000-2003; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Two old women, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Two sisters from the porch, 2003-2006; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Two wasps, circa 1977; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Uneasy fall, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Unseen, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Untill it's gone, 2008-2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Uses of frost, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Vessel seeking to achieve, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - View from the cabin, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Volcanic sky, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Waiting for blizzard, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Waiting for change, 2005; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Waiting room, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Walk in early autuimn, 2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Walled garden, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Walled garden, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Walt, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Wasps, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Watching wind, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Water failure, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Way out for the spirit (auction), 1979; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Way out for the spirit (auction), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - What's happening?, 2010; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Who chooses /red tree, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Who knows stone, 2007-2009; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Why today?, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Windows, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Windows, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Windows, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Winter morning, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Winter night, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Without thought, 2007-2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Woman by sea, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Woman from phoenix, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - You can't be in two places at once, 2008-2011; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - You know my name, circa 1984; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - You know my name early draft (waterbed), undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Zack pond, 2008; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - 627930, undated; Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Book manuscripts, 1986-2011; Series 1 Subseries 2
    Arranged alphabetically by folder/manuscript title.
    This subseries contains typed manuscripts of poetry and short stories books, inlcuding Stonecrop, Staying in Nowhere, Breathing-In, Caught Moment, Light from Another Room, Moving On, Rituals for a Journey, Reading the Tao at Eight, Being Human Wanting Something, and Eve. Some of the folders of manuscripts also contain correspondence from reviewers and publishers. The material dates from 1986 to 2011.
    - Being human ms, circa 2006; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Being human ms, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Being human, wanting something, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Being human, wanting something, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Being human, wanting something, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Being human, wanting something, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Being human, wanting something, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Being human, wanting something, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - [Book Manuscript], Undated; Series 1 subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Caught moment, undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)